question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, Chewbacca is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The IBM PC used an Intel 8008 microprocessor clocked at 4.77 MHz and 8 kilobytes of memory.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pokemon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Santa Claus is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "27 Club is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "John Williams composed the music for Star Wars", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Shub-Niggurath is a creature that was created by \tJ. R. R. Tolkien in his novel The Lord of The Rings.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Republic of Malta is the smallest microstate worldwide.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The United States was a member of the League of Nations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Ottawa is the capital of Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Sun rises from the North.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2016 United States Presidential Election is the first time Hillary Clinton has run for President.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable character of the 2015 RPG Undertale; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Portal, the Companion Cube's ARE sentient.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Rich Uncle Pennybags from the board game Monopoly; wears a monocle.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"DragonForce's Through the Fire and Flames is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The S in Harry S. Truman stands for Samuel.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2005 video game Call of Duty 2: Big Red One is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Season One Championship of League of Legends, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Ping-Pong originated in England","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]